Welcome to Redis University. Let&#39;s start our journey together.
Welcome to this chapter we&#39;ll cover all the basic data types available in Redis.
Powered by open-edX, our online learning platform guides you through video
tutorials and quizzes tracking your progress.
Forums are there you need help.
Teaching assistants are ready and waiting.
The course is also available on a tablet and a mobile device.
Ok now on to your homework.
We have a virtual lab set up for each one of you.
it has a Redis server running and comes with code samples and sample data for your learning pleasure.
And yes, that is an IDE running in a web browser with console access to the Redis Server.
Sign up for our free online courses, coming to a web browser to you this summer